Guide to the Rudolf Carnap Papers, 1904-2007 ASP.1974.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Annotated Offprints, 1910-1972; XXVIII.
  - Offprints of Carnap's Writings, 1921-1972; 4
    - "Inductive Logic and Science." Offprint annotated, taped-in abstract of lecture on p. 197; 2 copies of letter by Carnap, dated August 1953; one offprint of German translation "Induktive Logik und Wissenschaft" [published 1970 in Erkenntnisprobleme der Naturwissenschaften, ed. by Lorenz Krüger] (Box 118, Folder 77)
    - "Semantic Information." 3 offprints, 2 annotated, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 78)
    - "What is Probability?" 3 offprints, two with underlining, 1953 (Box 118, Folder 79)
    - "Qu'est-ce que La Probabilité?" 1 offprint, some underlining, 1954 (Box 118, Folder 80)
    - "On Belief Sentences: Reply to Alonzo Church." 2 offprints, one annotated, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 81)
    - "Meaning and Synonymy in Natural Languages." 2 offprints, one annotated; 2 reprints, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 82)
    - "On Some Concepts of Pragmatics." Philosophical Studies. 2 offprints, one annotated, 1955 (Box 118, Folder 83)
    - "I. Statistical and Inductive Probability. II. Inductive Logic and Science.", 1955 (Box 118, Folder 84)
    - "The Methodological Character of Theoretical Concepts." 2 reprints, 1956 (Box 118, Folder 85)
    - "I fondamenti logici dell'unità della scienza." 1 reprint, annotated, 1958 (Box 118, Folder 86)
    - "Induktive Logik und Wahrscheinlichkeit." 3 offprints, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 87)
    - "Beobachtungssprache und theoretische Sprache." Dialectica. Underlining, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 88)
    - "Linguaggio osservativo e linguaggio teorico." 3 offprints, one with light underlining, 1959 (Box 118, Folder 89)
    - "Theoretische Begriffe der Wissenschaft." (Part I and II). 2 offprints of part I, one annotated; one offprint of part II, annotated, 1960 (Box 118, Folder 90)
    - "On The Use Of Hilbert's ɛ-Operator In Scientific Theories." 3 offprints, one annotated, 1961 (Box 118, Folder 91)
    - "The Aim of Inductive Logic." 3 offprints. 2 reprints, 1962 (Box 118, Folder 92)
    - "Remarks on Probability." Philosophical Studies. 2 offprints, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 93)
    - "Variety, Analogy, and Periodicity in Inductive Logic." Philosophy of Science. 3 offprints, one lightly annotated, 1963 (Box 118, Folder 94)
    - "Signification et synonymie dans les langues naturelles." Langages. 2 offprints, one lightly annotated, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 95)
    - "Probability and Content Measure." 2 Offprints, 1966 (Box 118, Folder 96)
    - "Andere Seiten des Denkens." Interview with Carnap by Willy Hochkeppel. Philosophie. Annotated, 1967 (Box 118, Folder 97)
    - "Inductive Logic and Inductive Intuition." 3 offprints, 1 annotated, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 98)
    - "Statistische und inductive Wahrscheinlichkeit." 3 offprints, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 99)